credomen.com 2017-10-31

# Privacy Policy | Credomen

We respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognise the importance of protecting your personal information. We have adopted a corporate wide Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information that you provide us with.

If you are under 16, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about Primavera's Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before registering or placing an order with Primavera.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites maintained by other companies or organisations to which we link and Primavera is not responsible for any personal information you submit to third parties via our website. Please ensure that you read the Privacy Policy of such other companies or organisations before submitting your details.

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU AND HOW?

Primavera collects personal information in several ways when you place an order or register for a service offered by Primavera. By registering, you are consenting to the collection of your personal data. If an order is placed with us, we need to hold personal information including your name, email address, phone numbers, home address, shipping and credit/debitcard billing address(es) so that we can process and fulfill your order. Saved card details will never be shared with third parties and will only be used to process your order, using our Payment Service Provider's systems".

We may also obtain information as a result of authentication or identity checks. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.

In addition, our Live Chat provider stores all chat conversations for 13 months. These transcripts are only accessed by Primavera for training purposes so we can enhance the service we provide. 

MARKETING OPT-IN and OPT-OUT PROVISION

When you register, you will be given the option to opt-out of subscribing to our regular update service which will send you:

(i) Email alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions.

(ii) Direct mail alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions.

We do not sell or otherwise pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes. Marketing communications you subscribe to will only be sent by derodeloper.com.

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update to which you have subscribed, if you change your mind. Any e-mail we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that particular mailshot. Simply follow the indications in the e-mail. Alternatively you can change your email preferences or opt out of all emails by logging into My Account. 

#### WE ONLY PROVIDE YOU WITH THE BEST

Luxury Fashion For Men from all main international fashion designers, such as: Givenchy, Philipp Plein, Valentino, Balmain, Marcelo Burlon, Gucci, Dolce & Gabbana, Balenciaga, Dsquared2, Lanvin, Moncler, Saint Laurent, Neil Barrett, Off-White, Salvatore Ferragamo, Canada Goose, Moose Knuckles and many more.
